

Lucky Kashyap

SEO and DIGITAL MARKETING EXPERT

- +91 9897125409
- Luckykashyap4u@gmail.com
- Mathura, U.P. India, 281001
- s Luckykashyap
- in linkedin.com/in/luckykashyap
- +91 9897125409

ABOUT ME

With a Robust Track Record Spanning 10 years, I am a seasoned SEO and Digital Marketing Professional, Specializing in SEO, Social Media Marketing, Digital marketing, GMB Optimization, Ecommerce SEO, Shopify SEO, Google ads, Meta Ads etc.

I Specialize in managing high converting SEO Strategies and I have generated 5X ROIs for many Startups and Ecommerce businesses. I help startups, small, medium and big businesses to make it fortune.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Digital Marketing Manager (Remote) (30+ accounts)

Sep 2021- Present

Blink Digital, United Kingdom

- Created Dynamic SEO strategies to exceed market competitors and meet client needs.
- Optimized National and Local Businesses SEO Optimization, Google My Business Optimization, Achieved Top Page Ranking with targeted keywords. Using Search Engine Ranking Paid Tool.
- Recommended changes to website architecture, content and linking to improve SEO positions.
- Successfully Managed Social media marketing campaigns to create Brand awareness.
- Collaborated with editorial and marketing teams to drive SEO in content creation and content programming.
- Google Analytics Management, Goal setup, Custom reporting, Client communication and reporting.

Digital Marketing Manager (Remote)

July 2020 - Aug 2021

Dot Design Media, United States

- Translated clients goals and objectives into actionable and measurable SEO campaigns.
- Created SEO Strategies for National and International Clients, SEMrush Management.
- SMM (Manage Companies Account Facebook, LinkedIn).
- Successfully Achieved page 1 ranking for different industries websites Law, Travel, Accounting etc.
- Google Analytics Management.
- Google ads and Facebook ads account management.

SEO and Social Media Manager (Remote)

Top Notch Ads Pty. Itd.

2019 - 2020

- SEO Audit, Keyword Research, Content analysis, Technical SEO, SEO Strategy.
- Off-Page Activities and On-Page SEO.
- SEO Tools Moz Pro, SEMrush, Google Search Console.
- Created and edited content for different blogs, portal websites.
- SMM (Manage Companies Account Facebook, Twitter, Instagram, LinkedIn).

SEO and Social Media Expert (Remote)

2018 - 2019

Coastline Management Group, INC

- SEO Strategy development, Keyword Research and Competitor Analysis.
- Off-Page Activities and On-Page SEO.
- SEO Tools Moz Pro, SEMrush, Google Search Console.
- Created Social media content, Graphic design with Canva etc.
- SMM (Manage Companies Account Facebook, Twitter, Instagram, LinkedIn).

SEO Analyst (Remote)

Chicago Limos Inn Pty. Ltd.

2016 - 2018

- SEO Optimization for company website, SEO Audit, Marketing strategy, top ranking strategy.
- On-Page SEO, website management.
- Content creation and management.
- Created Social media content, Graphic design with Canva etc.
- Monitored Site Traffic, Backlinks, and Ad performance.

SEO Expert (Onsite)

iQuinceSoft Consulting Services Pvt. Ltd.

2014 - 2016

- Handled SEO Projects, SEO Audit, Marketing strategy.
- Keyword Research, Link Building and Competitor Analysis.
- Web analytic, Custom Reporting, trend analysis, client interactions and Reporting.
- Meta tag optimization, Robot files creation, Implementation of H1/H2, Image Optimization, Blog setup, XML Sitemap, Google analytics, off page SEO.

SKILL SET

- Search Engine Optimization
- Google My Business
- Meta tag optimization
- Link Building
- Ecommerce SEO
- Local SEO
- SEO audit

- Search Engine Marketing
- Social Media Marketing
- Keyword Research & analysis
- WordPress SEO
- Shopify SEO
- Google Search Console
- Facebook Ads

CERTIFICATES

- Fundamentals of Digital Marketing by Google.
- Digital Marketing Course and Internship.

EDUCATION

- P.G. diploma 2007 from Annamalai University, India.
- Graduated from D. B. R. A. University, Agra, India.

LET ME DIVE INTO SOME OF THE THINGS WHERE I AM EXPERTISE AT!

Advanced On-page SEO

- Keyword (such as KOB, VSO, Long Tail and etc), Competitor analysis.
- SEMrush Audit, fixes, visibility & position tracking.
- Metadata Creating.
- XML & HTML sitemaps.
- Robots.txt, Broken link fixes & Canonical Issues.
- Head & title tags, mixed content & duplicate content issues.
- Image & Content optimization.

Search Engine Console

- Resolving Crawl Issue, Prevent Hack & Monitor D.N.S.
- Disavow link monitor, Index & de-index look-up.
- XML sitemap verification & submission without errors.
- Crawling, Indexing, Broken links issues fixing.

Technical SEO

- Yoast S.E.O, Rank Math SEO, All in one SEO.
- Google Page Speed Insight fixes, G.T matrix fixes & Pingdom fixes.
- Website optimization for improving the user experience structured data.
- Rich structured snippet, AMP verification, Audit report issues fixing.

Social Media Marketing

- Facebook, Instagram, LinkedIn, X, YouTube, Pinterest profile optimization.
- Social Media Marketing Campaigns Increasing brand awareness, Increasing sales, Acquiring leads, Increasing engagement.
- Meta Ads, Google Ads, Facebook Account manager.
- Content Creating banners, images and videos to reach audience. A popular tool we can use to create images for campaign is Canva.
- Development and execution of a social content strategy posting updates, scheduling posts, social listening, collaborating.
- Engagement Responding and engaging with fans and followers to build relationships.

MY SEO STRATEGY

- Website Audit
- Website Optimization
- Competitor Analysis
- Customer research
- Keywords research
- Content Production
- Backlink Acquisition
- Performance Tracking
- Content tuning

SOME ACHIEVEMENTS

- I have developed comprehensive SEO Strategies for 100+ websites and achieved great results with competitive keywords for page 1 ranking.
- I have successfully achieved organic traffic growth up to 300%.
- I developed a fundamentally sound keyword research strategy, set timelines and commenced with Best SEO strategy.
- I worked on various SEO Audit to Fix technical issues, HTML, Broken links fixing and core web vital issues. Increased website health score up to 100%.
- I Successfully Created many Social media profiles and Managed organic and Paid marketing campaign to boost Brand awareness, boost Following, customer response.

Other Skills

- Excellent Knowledge of spoken and written English
- Strong Motivational, Interpersonal & Team-Building Skills
- Providing support to other production team members
- Ability to work under pressure and meet deadlines.

I, Lucky kashyap hereby declare that the above provided information is true to the best of my knowledge and belief. The relevant credentials would be given whenever required. (Lucky kashyap)